Miss Tang, you...
I'm going to find Yuwen Jia.
Before I come back,
if he...
Jingxuan.
If I don't come back safely,
I'll leave him in your care.
Miss Tang,
you must come back safely.
Jingxuan, wake up.
If I'm not mistaken,
you've recovered all your memories, haven't you?
I haven't forgotten anything I should remember.
Then there's nothing more to say.
Yuwen Jingxuan without the Soul Jade
is like a wild beast.
Even if you kill me,
how can he take on such a great responsibility?
Where is Miss Tang?
She went to Lord Yu to get the Soul Jade back.
It's useless.
From the moment I was born, that box
has recognized me as its master.
Yuwen Jia can only put the Soul Jade in,
but he can't take it out.
The same goes for Miss Tang.
But I hope Miss Tang
can successfully snatch the box back this time.
Once I take out the Soul Jade,
I will take the box back to Rouran.
You are going back to Rouran?
Why do you all ask the same question?
Xiyao.
Are you still unwilling to give me a chance to make amends?
You clearly...
I do like you very much.
But from the moment you sent me back,
it became impossible for us.
Miss Tang.
What's wrong?
I'm fine, Princess Xiyao. Don't worry.
It's a pity that I failed the mission
and didn't get it back.
It's okay.
I'll help you back to rest now.
No need.
I'll go see Jingxuan first.
Miss Tang.
If this is your fate with the Prince of Shuo,
what will you do?
I only know that
I must do my best in everything
so as not to leave any regrets.
Miss Tang, he doesn't recognize you now.
You'd better not...
Jingxuan.
Jingxuan, look at me.
Look at me.
Jingxuan, I can't fight
Yuwen Jia alone.
You must wake up quickly
so we can get the Soul Jade back together.
Do you know?
I know.
I know you can hear me.
I know you are still conscious.
When I asked you to take your medicine before,
you secretly used it to water the flowers.
Now you've learned to behave.
Why do you keep bringing up the past?
I haven't even scolded you yet.
You went to find Yuwen Jia all by yourself
and got covered in injuries.
Does it still hurt now?
You don't need to worry about me.
I'm fine.
I couldn't get the Soul Jade back,
but look,
Yuwen Jia couldn't do anything to me.
As for you, you must be good
and take your medicine.
Let's get well
and try to get the Soul Jade back.
I promise you.
I think I'm going back to Prince Yu's Mansion.
What did you say?
I'm going back to Prince Yu's Mansion.
If you return to Rouran, I won't stop you.
But as for Yuwen Jia...
I am Princess Yu.
You want to pretend to reconcile with Yuwen Jia
and then get that box back.
I know I'm in no position to advise you,
but Yuwen Jia...
Ah!
Su Zhiye, put me down!
Let me go!
Put me down!
This scene really feels like a lifetime ago.
What can I do for you, Master Su?
I would like to ask you for some medicine
that can make someone fall asleep
but is harmless to the body.
You want to use it on Princess Xiyao?
Yes.
Master Su, you make perfect sense when advising others.
Why is it different when it comes to yourself?
Although I don't know
how things will end between you and Princess Xiyao,
I hope
you can still respect her choice.
Miss Tang.
His Highness wants to see you.
Think about it carefully, sir.
What's wrong?
An epidemic has broken out in Binzhou.
Although the people I sent are capable,
they still lack someone who understands medicine
to find out the source.
You want me to go there in person?
It would be best if you are willing to go.
This epidemic came too suddenly.
I was caught off guard.
If it weren't for my health,
I would really like to go in person.
Then I will go tomorrow.
Then I will arrange it for you now.
What is it?
Just lamenting the hardships of the people.
Zhiluo.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Stay safe.
Zhiluo.
I hope you can understand my good intentions.
Wait.
Why haven't I heard about the epidemic in Binzhou?
Stop! Turn back to the manor immediately.
Don't come any closer.